areaconnect.com 2002-02-01

# 

**INTRODUCTION**  
The AreaConnect Network collects personally identifying information about you only when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us. The AreaConnect Network is dedicated to providing you with a compelling service to help you make the most of your time on the Internet. The more we know about you, the better we can serve your needs.

We recognize that we need to earn your trust, and firmly believe that you should know exactly what personally identifying information we collect and how we're going to use it before you share it with us.

* * *

**BASIC STATEMENT**  
Personally identifying information that you provide to the AreaConnect Network of sites will not be made available to third parties outside of the AreaConnect Network without your explicit permission.

The AreaConnect Network collects personally identifying information about you only when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us. Your personally identifying information will be used to personalize your experience with the AreaConnect Network Web sites, or for such other purposes as are described at any point where the AreaConnect Network collects this information from you.

The AreaConnect Network may make aggregate information about our customers (e.g. overall statistics) available to third parties for advertising and other purposes. Information that personally identifies you will be kept strictly confidential.

Personally identifying information which you choose to provide to another party or Web site will be subject to their privacy policy. For example, if you purchase goods or services online from a merchant you found while searching the AreaConnect Network, information you provide to that merchant is subject to their privacy policy rather than ours. 

* * *

**WHAT IS "PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION"?**  
"Personally identifying information" is information that can be explicitly used to identify and/or contact you as an individual. This includes information like your real name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, etc. Information that, by itself, cannot be explicitly linked with your "real" identity is not considered personally identifying. Examples of this are favourite or bookmarked Web sites, or your preferences with respect to how you wish to see a given page or site set up according to the selections you choose.

On occasion, the AreaConnect Network may ask you for personal information such as your name or address. We do this when you register for contests/promotions or services that require registration or subscription. The AreaConnect Network needs to collect this information for fulfilling prizes, and for tracking/verifying compliance with AreaConnect Network policies. It may also be needed for purposes of compliance with federal, state and local laws and/or for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes. When we intend to use your personal information, we tell you up front. This way you can decide whether you want to give us the information or not. 

* * *

**USE OF COOKIES**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site, like what items you have in a "shopping cart" for an online store. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide great features for their customers.

The AreaConnect Network has two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the AreaConnect Network service that our users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to the AreaConnect Network always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the AreaConnect Network service may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

* * *

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
Users should be aware that when you are on the AreaConnect Network, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from the AreaConnect Network pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement or a AreaConnect Network search result, the "click" takes you off the AreaConnect Network site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use the AreaConnect Network’s logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up!

The AreaConnect Network's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond the AreaConnect Network's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. 

* * *

**E-MAIL TO US**  
When you send us e-mail, we will use your name and e-mail address only to respond to the concerns you write to us with. Your e-mail may be shared with appropriate people within the AreaConnect Network to help us respond to your concerns and improve the AreaConnect Network.
